- Sheldon, can you grab me a water?
- Possibly.
- Can you or can't you?
- It's not that simple, Leonard.
(Leonard:)It never is, is it?
(Sheldon:)At this moment,
our relationship exists...
(Sheldon:)...in two mutually contradictory states.
(Sheldon:)Until you either do not go
or go to wil Wheaton's party...
...you are simuItaneously
my friend and not my friend.
(Sheldon:)I'm characterizing this phenomenon
as Schrödinger's friendship.
- Got it. Can I have my water?
- Yeah, of course.
Now get it yourseIf, you traitor.
- Wait, what is going on?
- ln case you have forgotten...
- ...Schrödinger's cat is a thought...
- No, I didn't forget.
(Penny:)Um, there's this cat in a box
and until you open it...
(Penny:)...it's either dead or alive or both.
AIthough our cat got stuck
in my brother's camp trunk...
(Penny:)...and we did not need to open it to know
there was all kinds of dead cat in there.